
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Process of inserting an element in stack is called",
    answer: "Push",
    options: [
      "Create",
      "Push",
      "Pop",
      "Evaluate"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Process of removing an element from stack is called",
    answer: "Pop",
    options: [
      "Pop",
      "Push",
      "Queue",
      "Stack"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In a stack, if a user tries to remove an element from an empty stack it is called",
    answer: "Underflow",
    options: [
      "Underflow",
      "Empty collection",
      "Zero collection",
      "Garbage Collection"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Pushing an element into stack already having five elements and stack size of 5, then stack becomes",
    answer: "Overflow",
    options: [
      "Overflow",
      "Crash",
      "Underflow",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Consider the usual algorithm for determining whether a sequence of parentheses is balanced. The maximum number of parentheses that appear on the stack AT ANY ONE TIME when the algorithm analyzes: (()(())(()))?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4 or More"
    
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Consider the usual algorithm for determining whether a sequence of parentheses is balanced. Suppose that you run the algorithm on a sequence that contains 2 left parentheses and 3 right parentheses (in some order). The maximum number of parentheses that appear on the stack AT ANY ONE TIME during the computation?",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + â€“ *?",
    answer: "-18",
    options: [
      "1",
      "20",
      "40",
      "-18"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A linear list of elements in which deletion can be done from one end (front) and insertion can take place only at the other end (rear) is known as",
    answer: "Queue",
    options: [
      "Queue",
      "Stack",
      "Tree",
      "List"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A queue follows",
    answer: "FIFO",
    options: [
      "FIFO",
      "LIFO",
      "ORDERED",
      "LINEAR"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Circular Queue is also known as",
    answer: "Ring Buffer",
    options: [
      "Ring Buffer",
      "Square Buffer",
      "Circular Buffer",
      "Linear Buffer"
    ]
  },
 
  

];